本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译：二川    女主很疯很爱笑    夜潇湘    小跟班    wdjmhs
翻译：饿得慌    zhanginfo            时间轴：Poxle    紫薰    三水
校对：zhanginfo      吃货丁小七       wdjmhs
后期：渔夫      精校：wdjmhs      字幕总监制：wdjmhs
国 土 安 全
第五季  第四集
《国土安全》前情提要
Previously on Homeland...
你看看她
Look at her.
她会因此发大财的  我们怎么不自己干
She's getting rich out of this. Why not us?
情报是免费的
Information's for free.
有个生意机会给你
There's a business opportunity for you.
我有东西要卖
Something for sale.
文件  绝密
Documents. Top secret.
美国的
American.
我先审一下  然后就发出来
I'll vet them and get them out just like last time.
我怎么联系你
How can I reach you?
你不能
You can't.
你个混蛋
You little fucker.
我们是老朋友了  索尔  你应该知道
We're old friends, Saul, so you should know something.
我的政府坚决反对
My government will actively oppose
任何在在大马士革进行权力变更的计划
any plans for regime change in damascus.
我们已经不干
We're out of the business
推翻阿拉伯独裁者的事了  因泰
of overthrowing Arab dictators, Etai.
我们可以行动了
We have a green light.
你觉得他们的情报有多详尽
How detailed is their intelligence?
他们知道目标是阿萨德
They know Assad is in the crosshairs.
知道我们有候选人可以取代他
They know we have a likely candidate to replace him.
是中情局那个女的  她是目标
It was the CIA woman. She was the target.
有人要你死
Someone wants you dead.
我不知道我能不能让她坐上明天的飞机
I don't know if I can put her on that plane tomorrow.
怎么不跟她一起走
Why not go with her?
那样还不如让她留在这里安全
If I do that, she's no safer than she is here.
不会再有支援  你不再是局里的人
You'll get no support, you'll be out of the agency.
从今天开始不要再联系
No contact from today.
你只有那把钥匙  下一个目标在盒子里
All you'll get is that key, your next target in the box,
等你带着她死亡的证据回来
and operating money waiting there
就可以拿到报酬
when you bring back proof of death.
麦吉森
我们得走了
We have to go.
马上离开
We have to go right now.
-他们已经在来的路上了  -谁
- They're already on their way. - Who is?
我是说
I am saying that whoever
要杀我的人马上就到了
is trying to kill me is coming here!
卡莉
Carrie?!
见鬼  你在哪
Goddamn it! Where are you?!
老天  我还真以为已经摆脱这种生活了
Christ, I really thought I left all this behind.
伊斯兰国极端组织宣布建立
The Islamic State ISIS proclaimed itself
全球性哈里发国  势力范围...
to be a worldwide caliphate with authority over...
重绘了中东地图
...Redraw the map in the middle east.
黑客成了士兵
The soldiers are hackers,
网络就是战场
the battlefield is online,
这不是关乎于...
And it's not a matter of...
爱德华・斯诺登是个懦夫
Edward Snowden is a coward.
令我极其失望的是  俄罗斯政府
...Extremely disappointed that the Russian government
将采取这一措施
would take this step.
这是违法的  这他妈是违法的
It's against the law, it's against the fucking law.
吃了这么多苦  还是什么都改变不了
All that suffering, and nothing changes.
我们的策略奏效了吗
Is our strategy working?
我之前竟然还说服自己我们能改变世界
I actually convinced myself we were gonna change the world.
卡莉永远都无法获得自由
Carrie will never be free.
过着逃亡的生活  放弃我女儿吗
Spend my life on the run, give up my daughter?
我不知道你的良心怎么过得去
I don't know how you live with yourself.
我会跟你抗争到底
I will fight you forever.
谁在追我
Who's after me?
死了这么多人  你手上沾满了鲜血
So many people, so much blood on your hands.
我们吃苦菜  这种苦味之草
We eat maror, the bitter herb,
来提醒自己不要忘记祖先们
to remind us of the bitterness of slavery
曾在埃及遭受奴役之苦
our ancestors endured in Egypt.
而我们
And for us,
我的亲朋好友们
my family, my friends,
在德国欢聚逾越节家宴
celebrating this Seder in Germany.
我们一定要记住
It is important to remember
仅在七十年前  我们在这里遭受的暴政
the slavery we endured under a tyrant worse than pharaoh
比法老更加残暴
only 70 years ago in this land.
在我们每日走过的街道上
On the streets where we walk every day,
我们父辈和祖辈却要佩戴犹太徽章
our parents and our grandparents wore yellow stars.
让我们默哀片刻
Let's take a moment to remember.
我们还要记住那些遍布全球
And let's remember the enemies we still have
想要毁灭我们的敌人们
all over the world who wish to destroy us.
我们祈祷拥有战胜他们的力量
We pray for the strength to defeat them.
奎恩
Quinn.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank god.
奎恩
Quinn?
奎恩  给我松绑
Quinn, untie me.
奎恩  这他妈是怎么回事
Quinn, what the fuck is going on?
你上了暗杀名单
Your name's on a kill list.
我知道
I-I know.
所以我才想不明白
I-I can't figure it out.
你肯定干了什么勾当
Well, you must have done something.
惹毛了什么人
Pissed off somebody,
触碰了什么底线
crossed a line somewhere.
奎恩  奎恩  不要
Quinn, Quinn, Quinn, no.
-不要动  卡莉  -求你了  求求你
- Don't move, Carrie. - Please. Please! Please! Please!
-别动  -不
- Stop moving, Carrie. - No.
我什么也没做
I-I didn't do anything.
不知道这是怎么回事
I have no idea where this is coming from.
我发誓无论达尔・阿德尔说了什么
I swear, no matter what Dar Adal said,
我都没...
I did not...
不是他
Not him.
是索尔
Saul.
索尔在名单上写了你的名字
Saul put your name on the list.
索尔
Saul?
闭上眼
Close your eyes.
我不信
I don't believe it.
你得信
Believe it.
先装个死相
Now play fucking dead.
好吧
All right.
赶紧  还有事做
Hurry up. We got shit to do.
什么事
What exactly?
你的撤退方案  可以启动了
Your fallback plan-- time to execute it.
我没撤退方案怎么办
What if I don't have one?
可能是真的呢
Could be true.
别废话了  卡莉  你得赶紧消失掉
Cut the crap, Carrie. Time to disappear and 'fast.
照片也就能拖延一下
This picture buys you time.
保持低调  他们才不会追杀你
As long as you keep your head down, they won't come after you.
你和索尔的这个行动  怎么进行
So, your operation with Saul- how does it work?
不重要
Doesn't matter.
告诉我
Tell me.
索尔提供名字  我杀人后拍照
Saul provides a name, I provide proof of death,
交回邮箱  再拿新名单
Return to the drop, get another name.
那你最后一次去邮箱是我的名字
And the last time you went to the drop, you got my name?
和你说过了
Told you that already.
为什么
Why?
不知道  也不想知道
I don't know. I don't want to know.
可我什么也没做
But I didn't do anything!
听着卡莉  你的名字的确在邮箱里
Listen to me, Carrie. Your name was in the box, okay'?
可能因为你还不知道的事情
Probably for something you're not even aware of.
我知道这不好接受
Now, I know that's hard to hear.
我得找索尔谈谈
I have to talk to Saul.
但你得知道  他圣命难违
For all you know, he was given a direct order.
什么意思
What's your point?
可能有某个高层要你死
Somebody, somewhere, likely very senior, wants you dead.
要是他们知道你还没死
If they think you're not dead,
还会派别人来搞你的
they're gonna send somebody to finish the job.
你得消失掉
You got to disappear.
你向我保证说你们不打算推翻
You assured me that there was no plot
巴沙尔・阿尔阿萨德政权
to overthrow Bashar Al-Assad.
-确实没有  -索尔
- There isn't. - Saul.
很荣幸你能光临我的逾越节宴会
You honor me with your presence
所以我也会与你默契
at my seder table, so, I'll play along.
如果你有取代阿萨德的计划
If you had a plan to replace Assad,
我们都明白会是约瑟夫将军
we understand that it would be with general Youssef.
约瑟夫是个好人选
Youssef would be a good choice.
如果我们计划是那样的话
If we had a plan like that.
他是阿拉维派的  阿萨德的连襟
He's alawite, Assad's cousin by marriage.
他在军方有些势力
He's popular with the military.
可有人说
Well, some say he was behind
他是阿萨尔镇化武袭击的幕后指使
the chemical weapons attack in Khan Al-Asal.
那些消息都没有证实
Those allegations have never been confirmed.
那我们换个玩法吧
Let's play another game.
还有其他选择吗
What's the alternative?
还留着阿萨德吗
Leave Assad in place?
阿拉伯人相互残杀时
When Arabs are killing Arabs,
至少他们不会向以色列发起攻击
at least they're not firing rockets at Israel.
对于中东的和平
That's hardly a long-term strategy
这不是长久之计
for peace in the middle east.
你还真以为那帮混蛋希冀和平吗
You really think any of those murderers want peace?
过去你是以色列的朋友
You used to be a good friend to Israel.
现在也是
I'm still a good friend.
你以前做得更好
You used to be a better one.
因泰
Etai?
今晚过得真愉快
I've enjoyed this evening so much.
很高兴你能光临这里
Well, I'm glad you could share it with us.
吃甜点吧
So, dessert. Mm.
我们要在一刻钟内离开
We need to leave in 15 minutes.
没事吧
Is everything all right?
当然
It will be.
你好  这里是卡莉・麦吉森
Hi. This is Carrie Mathison.
请留言静候回电
Leave a message and I'll call you back.
你回来了
You're back.
嗯  紧赶慢赶的
Ah, catching up.
卡莉呢
And Carrie?
还在琢磨谁搞的那次袭击呢
Still trying to figure out who was responsible for the attack.
我是想帮她  不过...
I was helping her, but...
我还是在这里更有用
we decided I was needed here.
奥托真该开掉她
Otto should fire her ass.
-她救了奥托的命  -她没做好本职工作
She saved his life. She didn't do her job.
她的工作就是保证老板的安全
Which was to make sure he was safe in the first place.
她建议过不要去
She advised him not to go.
你有事吗
Do you need something?
给我文档的线人把我耍了
My source for the documents screwed me.
他给我的优盘是空的
He gave me an empty flash drive.
-为什么  -我不知道
- Why? - I don't know why.
他可能害怕了
Maybe he's afraid.
中情局还在跟着我
The CIA is still following me.
好吧  要我做什么
Okay, what can I do?
你之前代理过的那个黑客  萨宾什么的
You had a client, that hacker, Sabine something.
她不会帮你  而作为她的律师  我也反对
She won't help you, and as her lawyer, I'd advise her not to.
乔纳斯  她很出名
Jonas, she's famous.
如果她出面  我的线人会回信的
If she reaches out to my guy, he'll respond.
她已经被软禁了三年
She's under house arrest for three years.
政府一直在盯着她
The government really went after her.
别去烦她了
Give her a break, hum.
-烦她  -对
- A break? - Yeah.
政府一直盯着我们所有人
The government's after all of us!
有什么事吗
Everything all right?
还好
Fine.
我在让乔纳斯帮忙找我的线人
I'm asking Jonas to help me track down my source
这样我们就可以得到余下的文件了
so we can get a look at the rest of those documents.
当然  帮她办了吧  挺重要的
Of course, help her. It's important.
有什么问题吗
What's the problem?
没有  我会去办的
No problem. I'll make the call.
越快越好
Sooner the better.
喂
Hello?
有消息吗
Anything?
没有  我回小屋找她
No. I drove up to the cottage.
她已经走了  所有东西消失  没留下线索
She wasn't there. Everything gone, no trace.
我们应该报警
We should call the police.
当然应该  但我们不能
Of course we should, but we can't.
她说那样她会更危险
She said it would put her in more danger.
她得靠自己来搞清楚真相
She has to figure it out on her own to get to the truth.
谁会这样过日子呢
I mean, who lives like this?
她会
She does.
我知道你很担心
I know you're worried.
我也是
So am I.
准备好了吗
Ready?
弗兰妮
Franny.
你的名字是根据你爷爷的名字起的
You're named after your grandfather,
弗兰克・麦吉森
Frank Mathison.
你知道吗
Did you know that?
我们好久没有见面了
We haven't seen each other for a while.
我不得不离开你
I had to leave you,
而你一定很生气
and you're probably really angry about that.
我不怪你
And I don't blame you.
不过  亲爱的  出了点事
But, honey, something happened,
我跟你在一起不安全
And it wasn't safe for me to be with you.
但我会尽我的一切...
But I am doing everything that I can to get...
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
如果你尽一切努力回到她身边
If you're doing everything you can to get back to her,
说明你还活着
then you're still alive.
-那又怎样  -如果这录像到了仇家手里
- So? - So, if this falls into the Wrong hands,
你就彻底废了
you're fucked.
我不会一直躲着的
I'm not going away forever.
只要等到事情解决就好了
Just until this situation is resolved.
这事怎么解决
How is it getting resolved?
我会搞清楚谁要杀我...
I'm gonna figure out who targeted rne...
-然后他们会一直找你  -我会搞定的
then they'll keep come looking for you. - And I will fix it!
如果他们认为你还活着
And if they think you're still alive,
他们就会通过弗兰妮找到你
they will get to you through Franny.
-但是  -卡莉
- But... - Carrie!
为了弗兰妮的安全  你必须装死
If you want Franny to be safe, you have to be dead.
天呐
Jesus.
你被迫离开自己的骨肉时是何感觉
How did you feel when you had to leave your kid?
不是所有人都适合为人父母
Not everyone's fit to be a parent.
继续录吧
Let's do this.
弗兰妮
Franny.
也许现在...
Maybe now...
你是"弗兰斯西"了
You're using "Frances."
我们已经好久没有见面了
We haven't seen each other in a long time.
我不得不离开你  而...
I had to leave you, and...
你一定在记恨我
You probably hate me for it.
我不怪你
And I don't blame you.
但是出了点事情...
But something happened, and...
我和你在一起会很危险
It wasn't safe for me to be with you.
我会尽...
I'm doing ev...
妈的
Shit.
我尽了一切努力
I did everything that I could
回到你身边
to get back to you.
但我没能成功
But I-I didn't make it.
我从事的那种工作...
The kind of work that I did...
非常危险
It's dangerous.
我忠于职守  愿意为它冒险
But I believed in it, so I was willing to take that risk.
但是...
But...
但是后来有了你
But then you came along.
我意识到我想改变自己的生活
And I realized that I wanted something different.
我想要  更好的生活
I wanted... a better life.
我和你度过了一段幸福的生活
And I had it with you for a while.
但是...
But...
我没有抛弃你
I didn't abandon you.
我知道被抛弃是什么感受
I know what that feels like,
我绝对不会抛弃你
and I would never do that to you.
你...
You...
你是最重要的
Are the most important, the...
我一生中最美好的事
The best thing
就是生了你
that I have ever done.
我人生中所有过错得以弥补
You make up for every mistake
只因有你
that I've ever made.
尽管你可能不相信...
And although you probably don't believe it...
我爱你...
I love you...
非常  非常爱你
Very, very much.
干什么
Was?
我找萨宾
I'm looking for Sabine.
这里没人叫萨宾
There's no Sabine here.
我和她约了见面
I have a meeting with her.
中间人是她的律师  乔纳斯・赫兰德
It was arranged through her lawyer, Jonas Hollander.
是吗
Is that so?
没见到萨宾之前我是不会走的
I'm not leaving until I see Sabine.
萨宾被软禁了
Sabine's under house arrest.
而德国联情局一直阴魂不散
But the BND keeps sniffing around,
想找出对她不利的证据
Trying to find something to use against her.
把她送进监狱
To send her to prison.
手机放进去  这袋子能屏蔽信号
Put your phone in here. It blocks the signal.
我已经把电话卡拿出来了
I already took out the SIM card.
要么把手机丢进袋子  要么滚出去
Put your phone in the bag or get out.
她来找萨宾
She's looking for Sabine.
你是萨宾吗
Are you Sabine?
怎么了
What's going on?
我才是萨宾
I'm Sabine.
你刚刚那么做是什么意思
What was that about?
我不得不谨慎点  抱歉
I have to be careful. Sorry.
我们知道你的丰功伟绩  太漂亮了
We know your work. Amazing.
萨宾不能和记者交谈
Sabine's not allowed to communicate with journalists.
这是她的软禁条件
It's a condition of her house arrest.
她是我们这边的
She's one of us.
她揭发了美国中情局和德国联情局
She exposed the CIA and the BND.
你搞得他们焦头烂额
You kicked their asses.
还能再火上浇油一把
There's more where that came from.
什么意思
What do you mean?
更多的文件
More documents.
-真的假的  -问题是
- No shit. - The problem is,
我联系不到那个"把文件黑出来的人"
"the guy who hacked the documents" I can't find him.
加布・H・库德
Gabe H. Coud.
-谁  -加布・H・库德  这是他的网名
- Who? - Gabe H. Coud. What he calls himself online.
-就是"傻逼"倒过来写  -你认识他
- It's "Douche bag" backwards. - You know him?
如雷贯耳  他很出名
Of him. He's famous.
他可是黑了美国中情局的人
Dude hacked the CIA.
你能帮我找到他吗
You can help me find him?
没有我找不到的人
I can find anyone.
你如果去找加布・H・库德
If you start looking for Gabe H. Coud,
就会招来不必要的注意
you'll attract the attention from the wrong people.
这简直是回到了前东德时代
This is like something from the Stasi days.
你们连个消息都不敢打听了吗
You guys are afraid to ask for information?
德国联情局巴不得把我丢进监狱
The BND would love to throw my ass into prison.
让他们试试看
Let them try.
我会让他们生不如死
I'll make their lives a living hell.
承担风险的是萨宾  又不是你
Sabine will be taking the risk, not you.
我也面临着被逮捕的风险  还有引渡
I'm facing arrest, too. And extradition.
我是疑犯  知道这意味着什么吗
I'm a person of interest. Do you know what that means?
意味着你不害怕
It means you're not scared.
意味着我在努力不害怕
It means I try not to be.
瑞士  杜维纳
约瑟夫将军
General Youssef?
我是
Yes?
约瑟夫夫人
Mrs. Youssef?
我是丹尼斯・凯勒  西弗尔诊所的负责人
I'm Denise Keller, director of the Seeufer Clinic.
这次安排的牵线人是德罗兹医生
The arrangements were made through Dr. Droz.
他在诊所里候着了
He's waiting at the clinic.
我妻子想跟我们女儿一起走
My wife would like to travel with our daughter.
好
Of course.
带约瑟夫夫人上救护车
Will you help Mrs. Youssef into the ambulance?
是
Certainly.
请跟我来
Come with me, please.
你待在飞机上
我和您一起  长官
这边请
This way, please.
在这里  您和您的家人享有完全的隐私
Your family will have complete privacy while you're here.
没有其他病人
There are no other patients.
捐献者呢
The donor?
他已安全抵达  并符合所有医疗要求
He arrived safely and meets all the medical requirements.
你不是瑞士人  你口音不对
You are not Swiss. Your accent.
您耳朵真尖
You have a good ear.
我是柏林来的
I'm from Berlin.
您女儿会没事的  我保证
Your daughter will be fine. I promise.
这是你的外科医生  德罗兹医生
This is your surgeon, dr. Droz.
我们电话里沟通过
Yes, uh, we've spoken on the phone.
一切都准备就绪
Everything is in order.
很好
Good.
请转交给肾脏捐赠者
For the kidney donor, as well.
我去准备了
I'll go prepare.
你想在阿妮娜被推进去之前
Do you want to spend a moment with Arnena
见见她吗
before they take her in?
好的  麻烦了
Yes, please.
我助手会带您去等待区
My assistant will show you to the waiting lounge.
如果有需要
If there's anything you need,
任何需要  请务必告诉我们
anything at all, don't hesitate to ask.
谢谢
Thank you.
你觉得他怎么样
So what do you make of him?
他是个什么样的人
What is he?
沉默  骄傲
Not a talker. Proud.
跟你想象中一样
Exactly what you'd expect.
习惯于发号施令  让人服从  不过
Used to giving orders and having them obeyed, but,
现在貌似是他的手下说了算
his officers seem to be in charge here.
他非常反感
And he resents that.
阿萨德肯定怕他会跑
Assad must believe he's a flight risk.
你觉得我们搞得定他吗
You think we have enough on him?
身为战犯
The war crimes.
女儿命悬一线
His daughter's life in the balance.
祖国形势又危险
The precarious state of his country.
我们有一手好牌
We got a hand of aces.
你觉得他会发火吗
You think he'll burn?
你又不是不知道  索尔
You know how it is, Saul.
这些家伙有的非常爱国
Some of these guys get all patriotic.
起码情报是对的
At least the intelligence is correct.
-他抽烟  -很好
- He smokes. - Good.
我也能会和他来一根
I might have one with him.
给他尝尝你的  他抽的叙利亚烟
Offer him one of yours. His are syrian.
他肯定愿意来点高级的
I think he'd appreciate an upgrade.
没问题
I will.
我得走了
I should get going.
是的
Yeah.
你搬到柏林
You moved to Berlin.
找了新工作  新男朋友
Got a new job, new guy.
却还保留着撤退计划
And still kept your fallback plan in place.
那又怎样
So?
我猜你觉得你的新生活可能不会长久
So I guess you weren't sure your new life was gonna work out.
我在这里过得很好
I found a good life here.
我本来很开心
I was happy.
你去哪儿了
Where have you been?
叙利亚
Syria.
奎恩  这过去两年中  无论我去哪儿
Quinn, the last two years, everywhere I went,
我都在找你
I looked for you.
我一直找你
I tried to find you.
我从没有忘记你
I never stopped thinking about you.
这些都不重要了
Doesn't matter now.
怎么样
Well,
我看起来怎么样
how do I look?
像个陌生人
Like somebody else.
你亲眼见到索尔用信箱吗
Did you ever see Saul use the drop?
-卡莉  别这样  -我必须要知道
- Carrie, come on. - I need to know.
是的  我们第一次建立联络时见过他
Yeah, I saw him the first time we set it up.
之后没见过吗
Not since?
没有  没有授权联络
I'm deniable. No contact authorized.
我们得走了
We have to move.
所以你并不确定
So you don't know for certain
-是不是索尔把我的名字放进去的  -天呐
- it was Saul who put my name in the box? - Christ.
你到底确定不确定
Do you or don't you?
这是索尔的行动
It's Saul's operation.
我只需要知道这么多
That's all I need to know.
没道理啊  我是说  也许索尔变了
It doesn't make sense. I mean, maybe Saul changed.
也许我把他惹毛了  但是索尔不傻
Maybe I pissed him off. But Saul's smart.
让你来杀我太傻了
Sending you to kill me is not smart.
太他娘蠢了
It's fucking stupid.
我活生生地站在这里就是最好的证据
The fact that I'm still alive proves it.
不论你怎么想  你都是个目标
You're still a target either way you look at it.
奎恩  如果不是索尔把我名字放进去的
Quinn, if Saul didn't put my name in the box,
你们的行动里就有内鬼
Then someone's inside your operation.
这之后你拿到的名字  都不靠谱
Any name you get after this, it's not legitimate.
我们试试看
Let's test it.
-带我去你的信箱  -不  我自己来
- Take me to your drop. - No, I'll handle it.
-我跟你一起去  -赶紧上车
- I'll go with you. - Get in the car.
带你去火车站
We're taking you to the train.
-不  -卡莉
- No. - Carrie.
你是说我在这世上
You are telling me that someone I trust more
最信任的人要杀了我
than I've ever trusted anyone is trying to kill me.
然后我还得乖乖面对  不能提出质疑
And I'm just supposed to accept that, no questions asked?
余生在逃亡中度过  再也不能见我女儿
Spend my life on the run, give up my daughter?
奎恩  我必须得搞清楚
Quinn, I have to know.
这边走  将军
Right this way, General.
请进
Come in.
这里有些表格需要您签字
There are some forms you need to sign.
不应该有表格
There shouldn't be any forms.
请坐
Please sit.
这是怎么回事
What is happening here?
我是中情局的人
I'm CIA.
这家医院的人都是中情局的人
Everyone in this facility is CIA.
当然  除了手术团队以外
Except for the surgical team, of course.
你来到日内瓦
You've traveled to Geneva in violation
违反了国际制裁条例
of international sanctions.
你在这里没有基本权利  没有豁免权
You have no rights here, no immunity.
我们可以逮捕你  以战争罪将你送到海牙
We can arrest you and have you transported to the Hague
接受庭审
to stand trial for war crimes.
你怎么能这样
How dare you?
继续盯着表格看吧
Keep looking at the form.
还有个办法
There is an alternative.
可惜  我们现在没时间讨论了
Unfortunately, we don't have time to discuss it now.
等到中午开饭
Wait until lunch is served.
如果你想抽根烟
Say you want a smoke.
就去花园里独自散个步
Go for a walk in the garden. Go alone.
在这里签字
Now sign the form.
谢谢  将军
Thank you, General.
你现在应该想回到妻子身边吧
You'll probably want to get back to your wife now.
还在找加布・H・库德
不在这里
我有事跟他讲
在找我吗
她气坏了
为什么
你把她玩了
盘是空的
胡说  我都给她了
找到他了  我们接上头了
Found him. We're on.
问他为什么给了我张空盘
Ask him why he gave me that bullshit empty drive.
他说他把那些文件给你了
He says he gave you the documents.
硬盘是空的
The drive was empty.
空的吗
Empty?
科赞尼克这个傻逼
Fucking Korzenik.
他说肯定是被他朋友动手脚了
He says that his friend must've screwed with the drive.
朋友
Friend?
到底有多少人知道这件事
How many people know about this?
科赞尼克
Korzenik.
你个混蛋
You asshole.
你怎么处理的那些文件
What did you do to those documents?
回电话
Call me back.
科赞尼克呢
Where's Korzenik?
走开  我在工作
Go away. I'm working here.
我要找你的白痴男友
I need to talk to your idiot boyfriend.
他不肯回我电话
He won't answer my calls.
出去
Get out.
打给他
Call him.
你联系上他  我就走
Call him and I'll leave.
亲爱的  我稍后就回
I'll be right back, baby.
你个人渣
You piece of shit.
科赞尼
Korzy?
你...
What...
你怎么处理的那些文件
What did you do with those documents?
放松  我们会发财的
Relax. We're going to be rich.
你卖掉了吗
You sold them?
你想把它们送人
You were going to give them away.
以自由的名义
In the name of freedom.
你知道什么才能让你自由吗
You know what gives you freedom?
金钱
Money.
我的俄国朋友出了高价
My Russian friend paid big.
俄国人吗
Russians?
他们派了辆车来
They sent a car.
别担心  我会算你一份的
Don't worry. I'm going to cut you in.
尽管你没资格拿
Even though you don't deserve it.
你不知道自己在干什么
You don't know what you are doing.
我不傻
I'm not stupid.
你个蠢货  给我下车
You idiot. Get out of the car.
科赞尼
Korzy.
这边走
Kommen.
科赞尼克先生
Mr. Korzenik.
进来
Come in.
鲍里斯呢
Where's Boris?
鲍里斯不在
Boris is not here.
我来负责跟你交易
You'll be dealing with me.
请坐
Please, sit down.
这是我同事  瓦伦汀
This is my, uh, colleague, Valentin.
瓦伦汀  打声招呼
Valentin, say hello.
我是伊万  很高兴认识你
Ivan. Very nice to meet you.
听说你有东西要给我
So, you have something for me.
我要先拿到钱
I want my money first.
当然了  抱歉
Of course. Sorry.
可以了吗
Okay?
-可以  -好
- Yeah. - Okay.
现在轮到你了
Now I need something from you.
很好
Excellent.
我们去检查一下
We will check it.
敬合作愉快  科赞尼克先生
To business, Mr. Korzenik.
合作愉快
To business.
这是唯一的副本吧
This is the only copy, right?
-当然  -你确定
- Of course. - You sure?
不会骗我什么的吧
Not gonna trick me or something?
只有这一份  我保证
It's the only copy. I promise.
很好
Good.
我得走了
So, I go now.
坐下
Sit.
拜托
Please.
要知道
You know...
信任别人是我人生中的一个理想
One of my ambitions in life is to be a trusting person.
我认为这是一种很可贵的品质  信任
I think it's an admirable quality, you know, trust.
那些与之相反的人  那些...
People who are the opposite, who are...
用英语怎么说来着
what's the word in English I mean?
-多疑  -疑神疑鬼
- Suspicious? - Cynical.
那样的人生可不会惬意
That's not a pleasant life.
所以你看  我想信任你科赞尼克先生
So, you see, I want to trust you, Mr. Korzenik.
不幸的是  我疑神疑鬼
Unfortunately, I am cynical.
真平静
So peaceful.
你不觉得吗
Don't you think?
我去抽支烟
I'm going to smoke.
你要去看看阿妮娜吗
Will you check on Arnena?
当然
Of course.
怎么  你不相信我是去抽烟
What, you don't trust me to have a smoke?
你觉得我要做什么
What do you think I'll do?
在我女儿手术的时候游到湖那边去
Swim across the lake while my daughter is in surgery?
午餐愉快
Enjoy your lunch.
约瑟夫将军
General Youssef.
索尔・贝伦森  我受宠若惊
Saul Berenson. I'm flattered.
请坐
Please, have a seat.
我们时间不多
We don't have much time.
要来一支吗
Care for one?
将军  你我都清楚叙利亚的危机
General, you and I both know the crisis in Syria
在日益恶化
is getting worse every day.
你指望我相信你关心我的国家
You wish me to believe you are concerned for my country?
我们的分歧在于你们的总统
Our argument is with your president,
不是叙利亚的人民
not with the Syrian people.
极端组织正在准备
The Islamic state is preparing
对政府进行一次大规模进攻
a major offensive against the regime.
所以
So?
他们占领着叙利亚的一半领土
They control half of all Syrian territory.
战斗减员和逃兵
Your regular army's been reduced
让政府军数量不断减少
through casualties and desertions.
说点我不知道的
Tell me something I don't know.
坦白来说  将军
Let's talk frankly, General.
你打不赢的
You will lose the war.
等到大马士革沦陷
When Damascus falls,
这个国家所有的阿拉维派
every Alawi in the country,
包括你和你的家人  都会被屠杀
including you and your family, will be slaughtered.
我知道你热爱你的国家
I know you love your country.
你一点都不了解我
You don't know anything about me.
我知道你是个有才干的指挥官
I know you're an able commander.
高级官员们对你十分忠诚
You have a loyal following among the high-ranking officers.
我们相信他们会支持由你来领导国家
We believe they will support you to lead your country.
领导我的...
To lead my...
等你取代了阿萨德
When you replace Assad.
这是你对叙利亚问题的解决方法
This is your solution for Syria?
这是当前最好的方法
It's the best one on the table.
一半的政府机构部长是巴沙尔的亲属
Half of the government ministers are Bashir's family.
全部非常忠诚  我要怎么解决他们
All loyal. How do I deal with them?
现在  我们正往你飞机上搬一千万美元
At this moment, we're loading $10 million onto your jet.
那些钱会给你买来很大的影响力
That money will buy you a great deal of influence.
巴沙尔也有钱行贿
Bashir has money to bribe, too.
但是你  以叙利亚新任总统的身份
But you, as Syria's new president--
许诺自由选举  民主改革
promising free elections, democratic reforms--
你会得到美国的支持
You'll have the support of the United States.
这支持包括军队和武器吗
This support, it includes troops and weapons?
我们会竭尽所能
We will do what it takes
让你们的政府统一全国
to unite the country around your government.
但是我们必须快点行动
But we must act quickly.
在你的敌人变得更强大之前
Before your enemies gain more strength.
你错了
You are wrong.
世界明白叙利亚真正的威胁
The world recognizes the real danger in Syria,
是所谓的伊斯兰国
the so-called Islarnic state.
他们一旦变强
As they get stronger,
巴沙尔就看起来没那么可恶了
Bashir no longer looks so evil.
世界就会改变态度
The world will come around.
他们会支持我们抵抗伊斯兰国
They will support us against Daesh.
如果阿萨德继续掌权
If Assad stays in power,
他就得为自己的罪行负责
he'll have to answer for his crimes.
什么罪行
What crimes?
铁桶炸弹  化学武器
Barrel bombs. Chemical weapons.
胡说八道
Bullshit. Lies.
我们看到古塔区的尸体了
We've seen the bodies in Ghouta.
阿萨德已经向世界承认是他的指挥官
Assad's already told the world it was his commanders
使用了武器
who fired the weapons.
他会毫不犹豫的送你上国际战犯法庭
Think he'll hesitate to hand you over to the ICC?
他不会指责我的
He will not accuse me.
我个人对这些事没有任何责任
I am not personally responsible for any of that.
我相信你
Well, I believe you.
我也相信阿萨德已经向世人展示
I also believe Assad has demonstrated
他为了保住自己的权力
he will do anything, he will say anything
会不择手段
to keep his grip on power.
将军  我们快没时间了
General, we're out of time.
我知道你是爱国者
I know you're a patriot.
你的人民已经受尽苦难
Your people have suffered so much already.
给他们一个前进方向吧
Show them the way forward.
带领他们走向光明
Lead 'em into the light.
他们找到了
They found it?
合作愉快
Yes. We're good.
谢谢
Thank you.
只有那一个备份  我发誓
There is just that one copy. I swear.
我留一份是为了...
I only kept it...
科赞尼
Korzy?
我进去  把东西放下
I go in, I drop it off,
就会得到名单上的下一个名字
I get the next name on the list.
那我们就等着有人来拿吗
Then we wait for someone to pick it up?
我们等索尔来拿
We wait for Saul to pick it up.
他一出现  我们就走
And when he shows up, we leave.
你逃得越远越好
And you get as far away from here as possible.
同意吗
Agreed?
同意
Agreed.
坐过去  我们可能要火速离开
Slide over. We may have to move fast.
你的朋友到了
我应该送你去医院
I should take you to a hospital.
不用  我没事
No, I'm okay.
你情况不妙
You are not okay.
我们得停车
We should pull over.
不  回去抓他
No. Be coming back to get him.
那人是谁
Who was that?
想杀你的人也想杀我
Whoever wants you dead wants me dead.
-你得去火车站  -不
- We have to get you to the train station. - No.
你的照片在信箱里
Your photo's in the drop.
你还没有暴露  你可以离开
You'll have your cover. You can go.
我不会扔下你
I am not leaving you.
我不走
I'm not.
看看后边
Check the back.
有个弹洞
There's an exit wound.
很好  是贯穿伤
Good. It went through.
不会打中动脉
Could've hit an artery.
否则我早流血流死了
I'd have bled out by now.
得给你打点吗啡
We need to get some morphine into you.
-架子上有个急救箱  -好的
- There's a medical kit on the bench. - Okay.
奎恩  还醒着吗
Quinn, you with me?
好了
All right.
转过去
Turn over.
好了  我要给你扎针了
All right, I'm gonna muscle it.
得使劲按住这些伤口
We need to put some pressure on these wounds.
好了  挺住  坐起来
All right. Hold on. Sit up.
挺住  奎恩
Hang on, Quinn.
我的同僚让我把这个交给你
My colleague asked me to give you these.
我有个请求
I have a request.
什么请求
What is it?
我希望我的妻子和女儿留下来
I'd like my wife and daughter to remain behind.
在欧洲生活  直到我们国家的冲突解决
To live in Europe until the conflict in my country is resolved.
我敬重您对家庭的牵挂
I admire your concern for your family.
但我不能允许
But I can't allow it.
你独自回到叙利亚会引起警觉
Returning to Syria without them would raise a red flag.
你们怎么知道我会干这事
How do you know I'll do this?
我收了你们的钱
I have your money.
我回到家  可以什么都不干
When I get home, I could just do nothing.
是的  你可以
Yes. You could.
但是我们赌你会更聪明
But we're betting you're smarter than that.
他问自己家人是否能留下来
He asked if his family could stay behind.
这是个好兆头
That's a good sign.
是吗
Yeah?
是啊
Yeah.
说明他知道自己被玩残了
It means he knows he's fucked.
说明他也许会乖乖合作
It means he might just cooperate.
通讯录里只有一个号码
There's only one number in the memory.
打过去
Call it.
我的天呐
Oh, my god.